More

Search...

Ctrl + K

* Why Choose Sonoran CAD?

* Other Products

* Tutorials

* Integration Capabilities

* Developer API Documentation

* Pricing

* Roadmap

* Other

On this page

Was this helpful?

1. [Other](https://info.sonorancad.com/other)
3. [Policy](https://info.sonorancad.com/other/policy)

Privacy Policy
==============

Learn more about Sonoran CAD's privacy policy.

**Privacy Policy for Sonoran Software Systems**

-----------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------

Effective Date: May 13th, 2024

### 

**1\. Introduction**

This Privacy Policy explains how we collect, use, and share information about you when you use our web, desktop, and mobile applications.

### 

**2\. Information We Collect**

a. **Personal Information**: When you register for an account, we collect your email address to identify your account.

b. **Technical and Usage Information**: Our services automatically collect your IP address, hardware IDs, and unique game and program identifiers. This information is used to aid in account security and our [alternate account detection systems](https://sonoran.link/oWGfTkf7).

**c. Cookies and Tracking Technologies:** We use cookies and similar tracking technologies to track activity on our services and store certain information. Tracking technologies used are beacons, tags, and scripts to collect and track information and to improve and analyze our service.

### 

**3\. How We Use Your Information**

We use the information we collect to:

* Provide, operate, and maintain our services
    
* Understand and analyze how you use our services
    
* Develop new products, services, features, and functionality
    
* Communicate with you, either directly or through one of our partners, including for customer service, to provide you with updates and other information relating to the service, and for marketing and promotional purposes
    
* Send you emails
    
* Find and prevent fraud

### 

**4\. How We Share Your Information**

We do not share or sell your personal information with third parties except as described in this policy. We may share your information with:

* **Service Providers**: We engage service providers who perform services on our behalf, such as payment processing (Stripe).
    
* **Law Enforcement and Legal Obligations**: We may disclose information to law enforcement, government authorities, or other third parties as necessary to comply with legal obligations or to protect our rights, the rights of others, or our property.
    
* **Account Security and Integrity**: While we do not disclose actual hardware IDs, IP addresses, or other specific identifiers to third parties, we provide the functionality for users to see if certain aspects of another user’s account match with alternate accounts based on collected data. This is part of our effort to maintain the security and integrity of our services, and [prevent fraudulent or deceptive practices](https://sonoran.link/oWGfTkf7). Actual identifiers are not shared externally.

### 

**5\. Your Data Rights**

You have the right to request the deletion of your personal information. You can do so at any time by contacting our support team at [support.sonoransoftware.com](https://support.sonoransoftware.com/).

Please note that while we accommodate most requests for data deletion, some specific hardware, software, and game identifiers are permanently retained to ensure the safety of our communities through our [alternate account detection systems](https://sonoran.link/oWGfTkf7).

### 

**6\. Children's Privacy**

Our services are not directed to children under the age of 18. We do not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from anyone under the age of 18. If you are a parent or guardian and you are aware that your child has provided us with personal data, please contact us at [support.sonoransoftware.com](https://support.sonoransoftware.com/). If we become aware that we have collected personal data from children without verification of parental consent, we take steps to remove that information from our servers.

### 

**7\. Changes to This Privacy Policy**

We may update this Privacy Policy from time to time. We will notify you of any changes by posting the new Privacy Policy on this page and updating the "Effective Date" at the top of this policy.

### 

**8\. Contact Us**

If you have any questions or concerns about our use of your information, please contact us at [support.sonoransoftware.com](https://support.sonoransoftware.com/).

Last updated 7 months ago
